Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 4"x5"
  - Ann Arbor
    - Buildings and Views
      - Streets
        - Huron Street, East
          - at Division November 1940 (Box 6)
        - Huron river Drive circa 1931, 5 negatives (Box 6)
        - Huron Street, West
          - at Main, looking east circa 1928-1930 (Box 6)
          - at Main, looking west May 12, 1932 (Box 6)
          - at Revena
            - October 15, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 6)
            - circa 1953 (Box 6)
        - I-94 circa 1960s, 2 negatives (in 1 envelope) (Box 6)
        - Ingalls Street at Ann April 22, 1964 (Box 6)
        - Jefferson at Division April 28, 1964, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Lawrence
          - near Division August 16, 1965 (Box 6)
          - near State August 16, 1965 (Box 6)
          - at Thayer August 16, 1965, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Liberty, East -- at Fifth 1963 (Box 6)
        - Liberty, West
          - at Main Street July 15, 1942 (Box 6)
          - at First December 17, 1963, 5 negatives (Box 6)
        - Main Street
          - at Huron
            - July 15, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 6)
            - circa 1942 (Box 6)
          - at Liberty 1948 (Box 6)
          - near Hoover 1963 (Box 6)
        - Miller at Spring Street circa September 1954, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Monroe at Packard circa 1966 (Box 6)
        - Packard
          - at Madison and Division circa 1960s, 4 negatives (in 2 envelope) (Box 6)
          - near State
            - 1963 (Box 6)
            - circa 1963 (Box 6)
          - at Arch 1963, 4 negatives (Box 6)
        - Pauline at Stadium circa 1964 (Box 6)
        - Plymouth Road
          - at Broadway October 20, 1959 (Box 6)
          - early 1960s, 4 negatives (Box 6)
        - Revena at Huron circa 1953 (Box 6)
        - Stadium Boulevard, East
          - at Westminster April 29, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - near golf course? July 29, 1954 (Box 6)
        - Stadium Boulevard, West
          - at Pauline circa 1964, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - at Liberty circa 1970, 6 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 6)
        - State Road at Waters Road October 28, 1963, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - State Street, South
          - at Liberty
            - circa 1937 (Box 6)
            - 1948 (Box 6)
          - at North University
            - circa 1930 (Box 6)
            - People walking in rain March 24, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 6)
            - circa 1938 (Box 6)
          - between Liberty and William 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - Nickels Arcade (interior)
            - circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 6)
            - circa 1930-1935 (Box 6)
            - Campus from Nickels Arcade circa 1933 (Box 6)
            - circa 1930s (Box 6)
            - circa 1942, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - near Madison circa 1934 (Box 6)
          - near Monroe (Law School) January 10, 1956, 3 negatives (Box 6)
          - near Hill 1963 (Box 6)
          - at Packard
            - circa 1930 (Box 6)
            - circa 1963 (Box 6)
        - Thayer at Washington May 21, 1937 (Box 7)
        - US-23 and Packard Road circa 1951, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - University, North circa 1932 (Box 7)
        - University, South 1964, 9 negatives (Box 7)
        - Washington, West -- at Crest 1951 (Box 7)
        - Washtenaw (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous Views
        - Aerial Views
          - May 15, 1937, 9 negatives (Box 7)
          - July 4, 1938 (Box 7)
        - Huron River 1945, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Snow Scenes March 14, 1937, 4 negatives (Box 7)
        - View from Cornwall toward Broadway April 22, 1964 (Box 7)
        - View from West Park July 10, 1937 (Box 7)
    - Businesses
      - Ace Cab Company -- Marguerite Sinelli, woman cab driver March 20, 1937, 4 negatives (Box 7)
      - Acme Broach
        - Interior and equipment 1951, 3 negatives (Box 7)
        - Interior with workers September 17, 1956, 4 negatives (Box 7)
      - Advertisers Publishing Company
        - Kitchen items, auto safety kit, calendar with picture of Detroit Maccabees building 1951, 5 negatives (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous promotional items 1952, 3 negatives (Box 7)
        - Staff party at Allenel Hotel April 1953 (Box 7)
        - Telephone and pad September 5, 1953 (Box 7)
        - Meat saw 1953 (Box 7)
        - T.V. table and hot plate 1954, 3 negatives (Box 7)
        - Kitchen items 1955, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Sunglasses and kitchen items February 1956, 4 negatives (Box 7)
        - Matchholder 1956 (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous promotional items March 10, 1962 (Box 7)
        - Tape measure and hot plate, watch circa 1965, 2 negatives (Box 7)
      - Airey house (George Airey -- building contractor) circa August 1955 (Box 7)
      - Alexander Drug. (Box 7)
        (See: 727 North University)
      - Alloy Metal Abrasive Company
        - Machines 1945, 3 negatives (Box 7)
        - Machines 1949, 2 negatives (Box 7)
      - Alloy Metal Products -- machinery September 3, 1953, 4 negatives (Box 7)
      - American Broach and Machine Company
        - Party at Allenel Hotel circa 1940 (Box 7)
        - Two men July 9, 1942 (Box 7)
        - Factory interior August 20, 1942 (Box 7)
        - Building exterior; plant floor, assembly line; men at work August 22, 1969, 10 negatives (in 9 envelope) (Box 7)
      - American Rug Cleaning Company
        - Men at work April 25, 1949, 6 negatives (Box 7)
        - Rug cleaning process 1952, 7 negatives (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Appliance
        - circa 1953
          - Portrait (Walter H. Berning?), 2 negatives (Box 7)
          - Kitchens, 17 negatives (Box 7)
        - Woman in kitchen March 23, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Woman in kitchen August 5, 1957 (Box 7)
        - Woman in kitchen August 6, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Kitchen August 7, 1957 (Box 7)
        - Woman in kitchen 1957 (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Construction Company -- men paving street May 1956 (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Dairy -- home delivery; woman in kitchen; woman in library 1949, 4 negatives (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Instrument Works
        - Gauge circa 1949 (Box 7)
        - Instrument May 1953 (Box 7)
        - Machine parts and shop interior circa 1967, 5 negatives (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Neon Company -- signs 1960-1965, 7 negatives (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Press
        - Interior with people working April 18, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 7)
        - Paper damage August 24, 1953, 3 negatives (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Tire Company. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 502 and 615-617 South Main)
      - Ann Arbor Well Drilling -- men and truck June 17, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor Wood Products -- toy truck 1948 (Box 7)
      - Antique Gallery 1952 (Box 7)
      - Arbor City Lumber company. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 521 South Ashley)
      - Arbor Enterprises -- cocoa machine August 26, 1961 (Box 7)
      - Argus Cameras, Inc. -- ditto machine and female operator April 22, 1954 (Box 7)
      - Arlan's Department Store. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses --2465 West Stadium Boulevard)
      - Armen Cleaners -- plant interior with workers 1953, 3 negatives
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 630 South Ashley)
      - Auto Parts Company -- group photo 1950 (Box 7)
      - Automatic Controls Corporation
        - Tom Thumb dishwasher brush March 13, 1951, 6 negatives (Box 7)
        - Sudslets dishwasher tablets March 15, 1951 (Box 7)
        - Automatic defrost display October 16, 1951, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Automatic defrost device 1953, 2 negatives (Box 7)
      - Beer Vault. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 303 North Fifth Avenue)
      - Bendix Aviation Corporation
        - Group of men February 5, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Space chamber April 5, 1961, 3 negatives (Box 7)
      - Benz Insurance
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 333 South Fourth Avenue)
        - Salesmen March 1939 (Box 7)
        - Salesmen May 1939 (Box 7)
      - Benz Motors. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 331 South Fourth Avenue.)
        [See also 2357 West Stadium Boulevard.]
      - Bermuda Restaurant. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 808 South State)
      - Big Ten Market. (Box 7)
        See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses --1928 Packard
      - Bimbo's. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 114 East Washington)
      - Braun and Brumfield Lithoprinters -- exterior and interior with workers and machines, early 1960s, 4 negatives (Box 7)
      - Brewery Products Company -- luncheon meeting of beer distributors 1953 (Box 7)
      - Broadway Norge laundry. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1120 Broadway)
      - Brokaw(R.T.) Company -- electrical engineering
        - Electrical equipment cabinet April 1953, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Electrical panel May 17, 1954 (Box 7)
        - Roscoe Brokaw and electrical panels circa 1954, 30 negatives (Box 7)
        - Roscoe Brokaw with truck May 1955, 3 negatives (Box 7)
        - Electrical panels 1958-1968, 16 negatives (Box 7)
      - Budget Shop. (Box 7)
        (See Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 611 East Liberty)
      - Buhr Machine Tool Company -- 839 Greene Street
        - Red Cross drive? (interior views with workers) March 1, 1943, 2 negatives (Box 7)
        - Interior with machinery circa 1951, 7 negatives (Box 7)
        - Interior with workers September 22, 1953 (Box 7)
      - Cabel -- lamp fixture and metal cup circa 1949, 2 negatives (Box 7)
      - Cahow Drug. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 213 South Main)
      - Calkins-Fletcher Drug. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 324 South State; 818 South State; 1101 South University)
      - Carlson Drug. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1112 South University)
      - Central Specialties -- equipment 1952, 2 negatives (Box 7)
      - Clague's Grocery. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1200 Packard)
      - Coca Cola Bottling Company -- Harold Kleis, manager
        - Coca Cola Employee Awards December 17, 1953, 4 negatives (Box 7)
        - Shop interior circa 1965 (Box 7)
      - Coffey Cadillac and Body Shop. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 215-219 Beakes Street; 502 East Washington)
      - Commercial Garage. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 117 North First)
      - Contract Purchasing Company. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 110 South Fourth Avenue)
      - Cousins Shop. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 307-309 South State)
      - Cummins and Barnard, Engineers -- architectural drawing of power plant for Pekin, Illinois December 5, 1942 (Box 7)
      - Curtis Chicken in the Rough; Curtis Restaurant. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 207 South Main)
      - Daniels Jewelers. (Box 7)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 201 South Main)
      - Danmar Products -- helmets June 5, 1971, 8 negatives (Box 7)
      - Dow Chemical Company
        - Consulting Engineers Division -- men and women in offices and laboratory August 9, 1940, 11 negatives (Box 7)
        - Product designs June 12, 1940, 10 negatives (Box 7)
        - Laboratory scenes with people 1948, 7 negatives (Box 7)
      - Duraclean by Byers -- rug and upholstery cleaning demonstrations circa 1970, 4 negatives (Box 8)
      - Dura-Bond -- adhesive bonding equipment
        - circa 1948, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - circa 1949, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - 1952, 2 negatives (Box 8)
      - Eagle Insulation Corporation -- dinner party 1949, 3 negatives (Box 8)
      - Economy Baler Company
        - Exterior and tractor circa 1950, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Machinery circa 1956, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Machinery October 20, 1960, 5 negatives (Box 8)
        - Machinery 1960, 3 negatives (Box 8)
      - Edwards Brothers, printers
        - Building exterior, 300 John June 9, 1944 (Box 8)
        - Machinery; men and women at work 1948, 25 negatives (Box 8)
        - Contest (portraits of women) October 13, 1950, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Contest winners? November 3, 1952, 7 negatives (Box 8)
        - Exterior and interior with workers November 1953, 24 negatives (Box 8)
        - Exterior, interior, and student tours February 27, 1956, 9 negatives (Box 8)
        - Yearbook kit April 12, 1956 (Box 8)
        - Interior November 14, 1957 (Box 8)
        - Workers and printed products May 12, 1970, 3 negatives (Box 8)
      - Elsifor Cartage. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Motor Vehicles)
      - Endicott Seymour
        - "Snug-Fit" plate hanger circa 1951 (Box 8)
        - Plate stand March 25, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 8)
      - Ernco's -- signs and lamps 1952, 4 negatives (Box 8)
      - Ernie's Black and White Shop (ice cream) -- interior with clerks February 5, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 8)
      - Ernst Electric Shop -- "Bug-A-Way" mosquito killer 1953 (Box 8)
      - Eskimo Art, Inc. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 314 North First)
      - Fenn Drug. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 103 North Forest)
      - Fiegel's. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 322-324 South Main)
      - Fingerle -- men constructing building 1960s, 4 negatives (Box 8)
      - Food and Drug Mart. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1423 East Stadium)
      - Fox Tent and Awning. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 624 South Main)
      - Freeman Grocery (Box 8)
      - Freeman and Clague Grocery. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 709 Packard)
      - Gallup-Silkworth Company -- man with signs August 26, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Gannon Painting and Decorating -- men with sign circa 1940 (Box 8)
      - Goldman Cleaners. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 214 South State)
      - Goodhew's Florist. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 225 East Liberty)
      - Haller (Martin) Company -- sofa bed circa June 1955, 3 negatives (Box 8)
      - Handicraft Furniture Company. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 337 East Liberty)
      - Hannah Construction Company. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 2310 West Stadium)
      - Hard and Company (food processors) -- machinery
        - 1947, 3 negatives (Box 8)
        - February 1954 (Box 8)
        - circa August 1955 (Box 8)
      - Hardt Company -- machine part design circa 1957 (Box 8)
      - Hart(R. E.) Manufacturing Company -- production counter 1953 (Box 8)
      - Hilbert's Garage. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1010 Pontiac)
      - Hoover Ball Bearing Company. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 326 East Hoover)
      - Household Finance Corporation -- interior October 27, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        [see also 219-221 South Main]
      - Huron Motor Sales -- sales meeting July 21, 1949, 4 negatives (Box 8)
      - Ivory Photo
        - Interior with man December 1, 1936, 4 negatives (Box 8)
          (See also: 606 South Main Street for exterior views)
        - Man at work February 13, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - Men photographing sports event May 1, 1937 (Box 8)
        - Clouds October 26, 1937 (Box 8)
        - Men looking at photographs (in Ivory Studio?) 1938 (Box 8)
        - Bud McDonald in Ivory shop October 8, 1939 (Box 8)
        - Julie and Bud McDonald (in Ivory shop?) November 29, 1939 (Box 8)
        - Clouds July 2, 1940 (Box 8)
        - Photographing Michigan -- Michigan State game (Mel Ivory?) 1940 (Box 8)
        - Frank Sidnorra, Ivory employee, in shop circa 1942 (Box 8)
        - Filmachine 1948 (Box 8)
        - Display negatives (Barry County courthouse; people) circa 1948, 7 negatives (Box 8)
        - Bessie and Isabelle (Ivory employees?) February 1953 (Box 8)
        - Mel Ivory's tax returns 1963, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - circa 1970
          - Ivory Photo interior and personnel, 4 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 8)
          - Mel Ivory as Santa Claus, 6 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 8)
        - Mel Ivory and daughter(?) in shop September 1971, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - Male model for camera club undated (Box 8)
      - Jacobson's -- models April 12, 1938, 5 negatives
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 612-620 East Liberty)
      - Kiddie Korner. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 564 South Main)
      - King-Seeley Corporation, manufacturers of automobile parts
        (See also 5"x7" negatives)
        - Women working; machine February 17, 1940, 5 negatives (Box 8)
        - Men working; diagram of machine circa 1940, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Timer circa 1941 (Box 8)
        - Governor December 7, 1945, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - Bowling champs (men and women) 1946, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - Gauges circa 1946 (Box 8)
        - circa 1947
          - Handy Hydraulic parts, gauges, governors, and other parts, 13 negatives (Box 8)
          - Staff party, 6 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 8)
        - Governor 1948 (Box 8)
        - Board meeting March 1951 (Box 8)
        - Joe Potter 1951 (Box 8)
        - Car dash and roast meter for annual report September 2, 1955, 3 negatives (Box 8)
        - Roastmeter; odometer and fuel gauge; speedometer; Continental panel; soldering guns; Mercury panel 1956, 7 negatives (Box 8)
        - Timer; meat thermometer; surface element temperature control; and other items circa 1956, 5 negatives (Box 8)
        - Gauges September 2, 1957, 3 negatives (Box 8)
        - Gauge and parts April 25, 1958, 7 negatives (Box 8)
        - Plymouth and Dodge gauges circa 1959-1960, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - Machine part circa 1960 (Box 8)
        - Governor (for Greyhound?) August 17, 1961 (Box 8)
        - Clock circa 1960-1962 (Box 8)
        - Timer September 1963 (Box 8)
        - Machine part undated (Box 8)
      - Kirby Products -- hot plates January 19, 1961, 2 negatives (Box 8)
      - Klean Sanitation Service -- men with truck and tractor July 24, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Kokales Frank'n Burger -- packaging August 11, 1969, 2 negatives (Box 8)
      - Kresge's
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 200-206 South Main)
        - Lamp display 1952 (Box 8)
        - Stationery display April 3, 1954 (Box 8)
        - Cosmetics display circa 1956 (Box 8)
      - Kroger
        (See also: 2111 Packard, 2545 West Stadium Boulevard, 224-226 South State Street)
        - Billboard ads circa 1952, 3 negatives (Box 8)
        - Display August 20, 1953 (Box 8)
        - Displays December 29, 1953, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Exterior 1960s, 2 negatives (in 1 envelope) (Box 8)
      - Krueger Hydraulic -- machines March 19, 1958, 2 negatives (Box 8)
      - Kurtz Building Company. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Motor Vehicles -- Trucks)
      - Lacy, Thomas -- advertising
        - Cat ashtray, alarm clock, and other products January 4, 1956, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Fishing equipment ads and other products circa 1956, 3 negatives (Box 8)
      - Lewis -- ceramics 1949, 4 negatives (Box 8)
      - LusTrus Extruded Plastics, Inc
        - Machinery 1951, 4 negatives (Box 8)
        - Machinery May 1953 (Box 8)
      - M Hut. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 322 South State)
      - MTM Association -- research laboratory
        - Group photo March 1954 (Box 8)
        - Group photos May 21, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 8)
        - Men at work circa 1956, 5 negatives (Box 8)
      - Manausa Motor Sales. (Box 8)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 320 South Fourth; 344 South Fourth; 1126 South University)
      - Marsh, Alvin -- Peaseway Homes dealer -- houses 1952, 5 negatives (Box 8)
      - Marshall Drug -- advertising circa May 1957, 2 negatives
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 235 South State)
      - Maurice-Roberts, Inc. -- toy wholesales
        - Christmas lights and toys August 8, 1949, 8 negatives (Box 8)
        - Dolls, children's furniture, and other toys 1951, 16 negatives (Box 9)
      - Mayer-Schairer Company. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 112 South Main)
      - Michigan Bell Telephone Company -- operators and switchboards April 1953
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 319 East Washington)
      - Michigan Dry Cleaners. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1031 East Ann)
      - Michigan Neon
        - Sign circa 1948 (Box 9)
        - Debugger (in butcher shop and laundry) 1952, 2 negatives (Box 9)
          [See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 327 East Hoover]
      - Michigan Scientific Products -- microscopes February 12, 1960, 2 negatives (Box 9)
      - Michigan Stoker and Engineering Company -- interior with machinery 1950, 3 negatives (Box 9)
      - Modern Appliance -- two men February 16, 1955 (Box 9)
      - Moseley Typewriter. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 114 South Fourth Avenue)
      - Muehlig (B.E.) Dry Goods. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 126 S. Main)
      - Nate's Boat Shop. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 909 Mary)
      - National Sanitation Foundation
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 2355 West Stadium)
        - Annual meeting November 21, 1946, 10 negatives (Box 9)
          [see also 8"x10" and 5"x7" negatives]
        - Men and woman in laboratory February 14, 1947 (Box 9)
        - Men in laboratory November 23, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 9)
        - People working in laboratories December 22, 1961, 8 negatives (Box 9)
        - Laboratory and man circa 1965, 2 negatives (Box 9)
        - People and display; waste treatment plant 49 circa 1970, 4 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 9)
      - O & W Distributors -- sign 1957 (Box 9)
      - Otis Elevator Company -- man and machinery circa 1956, 2 negatives (Box 9)
      - Pacific Finance. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 112 West Huron)
      - Parents' Pride Diaper Service. (Box 9)
        (See: Ann Arbor Motor Vehicles -- Trucks)
      - Payeur (A.H.) and Son Foundation Work -- laying foundation 1951, 2 negatives
        (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1643 South State)
      - Payne Products -- water heaters